# AHMED HEGAZY

# UI/UX DESIGNER

View My website

+201023870359



Tap here to view my Linkedin in



## **SUMMARY**

I have over three years of experience in designing user-friendly, responsive, and engaging websites and applications for various clients and industries. I am confident that I have the skills, creativity, and passion to deliver high-quality UI/UX solutions that meet your needs and expectations.

## **EXPERIENCE**

2022 - present

## **PAYSKY**

## **UI/UX Designer**

- Collaborate closely with product managers and engineers to understand user needs and project goals.
- Build UI mockups and prototypes to demonstrate functionality and interactions.
- Ensure consistency in branding, typography, colors, and imagery.

## 2021 - 2022

## **BENEFITS HERO**

## **UX Designer**

- Conduct user research, interviews, and usability testing to gather insights.
- Create visually appealing and intuitive user interfaces for web and mobile applications.
- Develop wireframes, storyboards, and process flows to visualize design concepts.

## 2021 - present

## **FREELANCER**

## **UI/UX Designer**

- Make products and services easy, effective, and delightful for users.
- Create aesthetically pleasing and functional interfaces for websites, apps, and other digital platforms.

## **PROJECTS**

## 2022 - present

#### YALLA SUPER APP

Yalla Super App is the first true Super App in the Middle East.

It provides fast, convenient, and secure digital services, some enhance made including:

- Ordering anything you need.
- · Donating to causes.
- Managing your finances.

Accessing the Yalla Money Ecosystem, Yalla Merchant App, Yalla PayLink, Yalla Payroll, Yalla Super Mall, and Yalla Bills

## Tap to View App

2022 - present

## MTN E-COMMRE PLATFORM

Momo Marketplace is a platform that operates in several African countries, including Côte d'Ivoire, Ghana, and Uganda

# AHMED HEGAZY

# +201023870359

## a7med.ismail@gmail.com

# UI/UX DESIGNER

Tap here to view my Linkedin in

- - Enhance user experience for Web and mobile app (Merchant dashboard, operation, super admin)

## 2022 - present

Tap to View

## **UPG (UNIFIED PAYMENT GETWAY)**

Revamp MOMO marketplace.

UPG (Unified Payment Gateway) is Egypt's national payment gateway that facilitates widespread acceptance of various payment methods.

## 2022 - present

## PAYSKY'S VIRTUAL POS (VPOS)

PaySky's Virtual POS (VPOS) solution turns any smart phone (Android or iOS) into a full-fledged payment acceptance terminal. It offers capabilities beyond what a standard POS can do

## 2023 - present

## PROJECTS UNDER DEVELOPMENT

- Governmental system
- loyalty program
- VAT collection system
- Payform

## **EDUCATION**

2020 - 2021

## **INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY INSTITUTE (ITI)**

UI/UX Designer-Intensive Training Program

2013 - 2017

## **CAIRO UNIVERSITY**

Bachelor's Degree, agricultural engineering

## **CERTIFICATES**

- User Experience (UX) Design by Google
- UX Design at Edraak
- UX Design Fundamentals Maharatech
- Freelancing Basics at Maharatech
- Customer relationship management "CRM" ,Supply chain basic, and Marketing" at school of continuing education AUC

## **SKILLS**

- UX Research
- Figma

• Responsive Design

- Wireframes
- Sketch

Revamp

- Prototypes
- Adobe XD
- Adobe XD

Mockups

- User Experience

- User Flows
- Usability Testing

Micro interactions

User Interface